What are you looking at?
What can you see?
Hey, Missy, are you waiting for someone?
お嬢ちゃん　誰かと待ち合わせ
Actually, I think I saw you here yesterday, too.
そういえば　お嬢ちゃん
昨日もここで見かけたけど　ずっとここに立ってるの
Have you been standing here the entire time?
もしかして人形だったりして
Maybe she's a doll.
Oh, she blinked!
今瞬きした
Woah!
動いた
She moved!
Huh?
Me?
私？
Found you.
見つけた
This can't be good.
これはまずい
そ
の
重
い
足
を
膝
前
へ
導
く
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
その重い足を膝を前へ導く
负
责
人
Maki
负责人
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
力
は
何
だ
っ
て
Go
ahead
問
う
力は何だって Go ahead 問う
君
の
中
に
生
じ
る
衝
動
は
treasure
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
君の中に生じる衝動はtreasure
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
日
听
小
伍
长
田
Cris
翻
译
兰
樱
Naga
校
对
小
伍
江
本
物
か
偽
物
か
つ
れ
て
行
け
よ
日听
小伍
长田Cris
翻译
兰樱
Naga
校对
小伍
小江
本物か偽物か つれて行けよ
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
空
想
の
彼
方
ま
で
僕
の
中
怠
慢
よ
空想の彼方まで 僕の中の怠慢よ
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
时
间
轴
阿
水
压
制
Coolkid
さ
ら
っ
て
も
い
よ
夢
で
も
时间轴
阿水
压制
Coolkid
さらってもいいよ 夢でも
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
届
き
そ
う
で
届
か
な
い
make
some
noise
届きそうで届かない make some noise
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
空
虚
な
日
常
は
輝
き
出
す
の
か
空虚な日常は輝き出すのか
吐
き
出
す
よ
う
に
し
て
前
に
漕
げ
ば
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
吐き出すようにして前に前に漕げば
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
僕
ら
の
未
来
は
加
速
し
て
い
く
だ
ろ
う
僕らの未来は加速していくだろう
今
こ
の
時
が
止
ま
る
と
し
て
も
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
今この時が止まるとしても
こ
の
呼
吸
ま
で
止
め
ら
れ
は
し
な
い
さ
この呼吸まで止められはしないさ
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
く
だ
ら
な
い
くだらない
ご
褒
美
ま
だ
？
ご褒美まだ？
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
Dazai has disappeared?
太宰が行方不明？
He hasn't been answering his phone,
電話も繋がりませんし　下宿にも帰っていないようで
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
and he hasn't returned to the dorm, either.
诸神微信公众号正式上线啦，搜索「诸神字幕组」添加关注吧
He's just floating in some river again.
どうせまた川の中だ
拘置所にいるパターンかも
Or he could be in prison this time.
女とどっかに行ったと見た
My guess is he left to flirt with a woman.
But it's true that he's targeted by the Port Mafia.
けどポートマフィアに狙われているのは確かですし
It could be that...
もしかしたら…
That man's ability to sense danger and stay alive approaches nightmarish proficiency.
あの男の危機察知能力と生命力は悪夢の域だ
あれだけ自殺未遂を重ねても　まだピンピンしていますもんね
Just think about how he's as healthy as can be
despite numerous suicide attempts.
マフィア如きに後れを取るとは思えんな
I doubt the Mafia alone will be enough to get the better of him.
でも…
But...
I'll investigate it.
ボクが調べておくよ
Are you all better now, Tanizaki-san?
谷崎さん　もう大丈夫なんですか
Yes, thankfully.
おかげさまで
I was really worried when it all happened.
あの時はどうなることかと思いましたけど
ほんとよかったです
I'm relieved you're fine.
I'm sorry I worried you.
心配掛けちゃったね
やっと回復したか
So you've finally recovered.
与謝野先生の治療の賜物です
It's all thanks to Dr. Yosano's treatment.
So, how many times did she get you?
それで　何度やられた
F-F-Four times.
よよ…四回です
四回も
That many...
敦君　この探偵社にいる間は　怪我だけは絶対にしちゃ駄目だよ
Atsushi-kun...
As long as you remain at the Agency,
remember to never get injured.
Okay.
まずいと思ったらすぐ逃げる
If you think you're at any risk, run.
危機察知能力を日頃から養っておくことだね
You should cultivate your ability to sense danger every day.
For example, ten seconds from now...
例えば今から十秒後
Oh, Dr. Yosano.
与謝野先生　お早う御座います
Good morning.
Oh, Atsushi.
敦かい
Are you hurt anywhere?
どっか怪我してない
Oh, I'm fine.
ええ　大丈夫ですけど
Damn.
ちぇっ
Damn?
ちぇ？
I was hoping to have someone accompany me on a shopping trip,
誰かに買い物付き合ってもらおうと思ったけど
but I guess you're the only one available.
あんたしかいないようだね
What?
Is this what he meant by the ability to sense danger?
危機察知能力って　これ？
D-Dr. Yosano, are you still not done?
よ…与謝野先生　まだ買うんですか
Don't you dare drop anything.
落とすんじゃないよ
What the hell do you think you're doing?
何をやってるんだ　全く　この給金泥棒が
You failure!
Hurry up and send my car over!
早く迎えを寄越せ
Ow...
いたたた
U-Um, are you okay?
あの　大丈夫ですか
Why did you do that, you damn brat?
どういう心算だ　小僧
This is a custom suit from Europe.
欧州デザインの特別誂えだぞ
S-Sorry.
す…すみません
I'm very sorry.
申し訳ありません　お怪我は
Were you hurt?
触るな
Don't touch me.
I'll file a complaint with your employer!
この件は君の所属企業に抗議させてもらおう
おい　仕事はなんだ
Hey, what's your job?
Are you a tea server?
お茶汲みか？　接客女か？
A receptionist?
Or perhaps you're something more specialized?
それとも　もう少し特殊な業務かな
Hmm.
Ow!
いたたたたたた…
I'm a doctor, you pervert.
妾は医者だよ　エロオヤジ
What's this?
おや　あんた腕が二本もあるね
You have two arms? That's too many.
多すぎて不便だろ
Would you like me to remove one?
一本とってやろうか
Episode 8
Teaching Them To Kill;
Then To Die
I'm sorry about... um... earlier.
先刻は…その　すいません
The packages are in a sorry state, too.
荷物もこんなことになっちゃって
気にすることはないよ
Don't worry about it.
By the way...
ところでさ
What?
なに　お仕置き？
Is this punishment?
Hmm, nice leg.
綺麗なもんだね
I heard your leg was bitten off
あんた　谷崎がやられた時
by the Port Mafia when Tanizaki got injured.
ポートマフィアに脚を喰い千切られたそうじゃないか
No signs of scarring or fusion.
癒合痕も瘢痕もない
It's more restoration than regeneration.
再生というより　復元だ
The tiger did this instantly?
虎はこれを一瞬で…
Um...
あの…
Is there a problem?
何か問題でも
Oh, I'm just sad I couldn't treat you.
なーに　妾が治療できなくて残念だって話さ
But there'll be no mercy from me next time.
でも　次はないよ
What?
The Mafia is known for surprise attacks.
元来マフィアってのは奇襲夜討が本分だ
You should watch yourself at night.
夜道にゃ気をつけるんだね
You never know when they may strike next.
いつどこで襲ってくるかわかんないよ
That's right.
そうだ　マフィアの一番の狙いは僕
I'm their prime target.
I should know how to defend myself.
自分の身は自分で守らないと
Testing, testing. This is your train conductor.
あー　テステス
こちら車掌室
誠に勝手ながら　ただいまよりささやかな「物理学実験」を行いま～す
We apologize for the discomfort, but we shall now conduct a minor physics experiment!
The topic: Evaluation of an Explosive Reaction and Sensory Response
題目は「非慣性系における爆轟反応および官能評価」
in a Non-Inertial Reference Frame.
試験者はお乗りあわせの皆様　ご協力　誠に感謝
The test subjects will be our current passengers!
We greatly appreciate your cooperation!
So, without further ado,
では　早速ですが　これをお聞きくださ～い
please listen to this!
Maybe two or three of
you died from that one?
今ので二三人は死んじゃったかな
But that will pale in comparison to the next one!
でも　次はこんなもんじゃありません
We've rigged enough explosives
in the front and back cars
皆様が月まで飛べる量の爆弾が先頭と最後尾の車両に仕掛けられておりま～す
to blow everyone clear to the moon!
Now, test subject Atsushi-kun.
さてさて　試験者の敦君
Unless you surrender yourself,
君が首を差し出さないと　乗客全員
all passengers will go straight to heaven, maybe even the moon!
月どころか天国に逝っちゃうぞ
そんな…
But...
云った傍から御出ましってわけだ
Speak of the devil...
ど　どうしましょう
Wh-What should we do?
Option one, turn yourself in.
一　大人しく捕まる
Option two, jump off this running train with several dozen passengers to escape.
二　走るこの列車から乗客数十人と一緒に跳び降りて脱出
三…
Option three...
give them hell.
連中をぶっ飛ばす
上等だ
Excellent.
After all, we are the Armed Detective Agency.
何しろ妾らは武装探偵社だからね
Okay, Atsushi.
却説　敦　手分けして爆弾を探すよ
Let's split up and locate the bombs.
I'll take the front.
妾は前方　あんたは後方だ
You take the rear.
What if we find the enemy?
もし敵がいたら
Terminate with extreme prejudice.
ぶっ殺せ
Roger!
了解
A bomb threat, on a train with civilians, in broad daylight,
一般人も乗ってる白昼の列車に自爆紛いの脅迫
that's essentially suicide.
Even for the Port Mafia, this plan's pretty bold.
ポートマフィアの謀にしてもえらい覚悟
いや　執着だね
Or, rather, obsessive.
I wonder who's behind this.
いったいどんな奴が…
Our warmest welcome to the decisive lady from the Detective Agency
果断なる探偵社のご婦人よ　ようこそ
and our most regretful farewell!
そして　さようなら～
Well, well,
おやおや
if it isn't a celebrity we've got here.
誰かと思えば有名人じゃないか
Oh, you're still alive?
ほう　生きてた
What a surprise.
こいつは驚きだな
Ladies are so resilient these days.
最近の女性は頑丈だ
It is an era of equality for men and women.
男女同権の世だからね
From where I stand,
妾からすりゃ　あんたみたいな指名手配犯がこんな処にいるほうが驚きだよ
it's a greater surprise to find a wanted criminal like you in a place like this.
Kajii Motojirou!
梶井基次郎
While being a member of the secretive Port Mafia,
隠密主義のポートマフィアの中にあって
珍しく名が知れた爆弾魔
you're a surprisingly infamous terrorist bomber.
Port Mafia
Operative
Kajii
Motojirou
Port Mafia
Operative
Kajii
Motojirou
Ability:
Lemon Bomb
In the recent Marizen Building Bombing,
先日の丸善ビル爆破事件では　一般人二十八人を殺してる
where you murdered 28 civilians.
That was most wondrous.
あれは素晴らしかったよ
The slowing of the pulse,
拍動の低下
神経細胞の酸欠死
the hypoxia of neurons!
Lactic acidosis...
乳酸アシドーシス
Death is the collective music of infinite changes in states!
死とは無数の状態変化の複合音楽だ
Ah, then comes irreversible death.
そして訪れる不可逆の死
So you're saying death is an experiment?
死が実験だって？
Science, in its final form, is God and death.
科学の究極とは神と死
Both exist and cannot be overcome by science.
どちらも実在し　しかし科学で克服できず
故に我らを惹きつける
That is why we are drawn to them.
So,
却説
what color is your blood?
あなたの血は何色かな
See for yourself.
確かめてみな
If we can't remove the bombs, these people will die.
爆弾を撤去できないと　この人達が死ぬ
But can I do this?
だけどできるのか　僕に
Hey!
君　駄目だ　そっちには爆弾が
Don't go that way! There's a bomb!
Please go back to the central car.
中央の車両に戻ってください
There's a bomb in the rear car.
後部車両には爆弾が
Um, you...
あの　君…
Your duty is to protect the bomb at any cost.
お前の任務は爆弾の死守だ
You're...
君は…
You're the one I saw.
あの時の…
Use your ability, Demon Snow,
邪魔者は殺せ
to kill anyone who interferes.
お前の異能力　「夜叉白雪」で
What?
Port Mafia
Assassin
Izumi Kyouka
Port Mafia
Assassin
Izumi Kyouka
Ability:
Demon Snow
Shred your enemies, Demon Snow.
敵のことごとくを切り刻め　夜叉白雪
Sh... She's too strong!
つ…強すぎる
Wh-Why?
な…なんで
Why would a girl like you...
君みたいな女の子が…
My name is Kyouka,
私の名は鏡花
an orphan like you.
あなたと同じ孤児
I like bunny rabbits and tofu.
好きなものは兎と豆腐
I hate dogs and lightning.
嫌いなものは狗と雷
After the Port Mafia took me in,
ポートマフィアに拾われ
I killed 35 people in six months.
六ヶ月で３５人殺した
Protect the bomb,
爆弾を守れ　そして邪魔者は殺せ
and kill anyone who interferes.
The Agency isn't as formidable as I've heard.
噂ほどじゃないなー　探偵社っていうのも
Oh, well.
まあいいや
So you're about to die, but tell me this before you do:
これから君は死ぬわけだけど　その前に教えてくれよ
What does it mean to die?
死ぬって何？
What did you say?
なんだって
Oh, it's just scholarly interest.
なーに　学術的な興味だよ
I'm an avid researcher, you see.
僕は学究の徒だからね
All the reasons for human death,
人の死因　脳細胞の酸欠もテロメアの摩耗も
including hypoxia of neurons in the brain and telomere degradation,
are simple reversible
processes in laboratory settings.
実験室レヴェルでは単純で可逆的な反応だ
Yet, why is death irreversible?
なのに何故死は不可逆なのだ
何故人はいずれ必ず死ぬ
Why must all humans die?
You don't even know why?
そんなこともわからんのかい
So the Mafia isn't so formidable, after all.
大したことないねー　マフィアってのも
You claim that someone who's a meddling private eye
理学の求道者たるこの梶井が知らないことを
街の便利屋探偵がわかるとでも？
would know something that I, a follower of science, do not?
Sure I would.
わかるとも　理由は簡単だ
The reason for that is simple.
あんたが阿呆だからさ
You're just an idiot.
Thank you for your precious opinion.
参考になる意見をどうも
I think you would know this, being well-read and all,
博学の君なら当然知ってると思うけど
but even after the body dies from blood loss,
出血多量で死んだ後も　脳と意識は八時間生きているそうだ
the brain and your consciousness can survive for eight hours.
Afterwards, I'll ask your corpse this:
後で君の死体に聞いてみるよ
"You're dead now. How do you feel?"
「死んだけど今どんな気分」ってね
Well, take your time.
それじゃ　ごゆっくり～
It's impossible.
無理だ　勝てるわけない
I can't win.
Will I die here?
僕はここで死ぬのか
Are people going to die again because of me?
またこの人達が僕の所為で
Just because they boarded the same train as me?
僕と同じ電車に乗った　ただそれだけの所為でみんな死ぬ
Just for that simple reason, they'll all die.
That is your karma, weretiger.
それが貴様の業だ　人虎
You cause harm to everyone around you, just by existing.
貴様は生きてるだけで周囲の人間を損なう
出ていけ　穀潰し
Get out, you failure!
The world would be a better place if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
どこぞで野垂れ死んだほうが世間様の為よ
穀潰しはこの施設には要らん
We don't need worthless louts!
Why are you alive?
貴様は何故生きている
You accomplish nothing,
周囲に迷惑と不幸を振りまき　何一つ成し遂げぬ者に
and cause inconvenience and
misfortune for everyone around you.
誰も救わぬ者に生きる価値などない
Those who can save no one do not deserve to live.
Just then, an idea popped into my head.
その時　唐突にある発想が浮かんだ
It was a stupid idea.
莫迦げた発想だ
But I couldn't shake it off.
でも頭から離れない
If I...
もし僕がここにいる乗客を
If I could save them,
the passengers here...
彼らを救い
If I could return them safe and sound to their homes,
無事家に返せたら
wouldn't that mean
そうしたら
that I...
僕は…
Wouldn't that mean it's okay for me to live?
生きていてもいいってことにならないだろうか
Stay away.
来ないで
Sorry.
ごめん
I can't do this anymore!
もう無理だ
She's too fast.
速すぎる
I guess I can't do this, after all.
矢っ張り無理なのか
If only I could use my ability...
せめて今　あの力があれば…
All right.
さーて
I wonder if she's nice and cooked all the way through now.
中までこんがり火が通ったかなー
Let's see.
どれどれ～
Hmm, that was underwhelming.
今一だね　もっと吹っ飛ぶかと思ったが
I was hoping you'd go flying a bit farther.
H-How?
な…何故
あんなネズミ花火で死ぬもんか
That little sparkler wouldn't kill me.
Which side did I punch you on just now?
今殴ったのどっち側だっけ
I-I-If I had to choose, maybe this side?
どどど…どちらかというとこっちより…
Impossible!
そんな　先刻まで瀕死だった筈
You were just on the brink of death before!
I may not look like it, but I am a doctor.
こう見えても妾は医者でね
I've seen at least a hundred times
more deaths than you.
あんたの百倍は死を見てる
What's death, you ask?
死とは何かって
教えてやるよ
Let me tell you.
Death is the loss of life.
死は命の喪失さ
No matter how hard we doctors try,
妾達医者がどんなに手を尽くしても　患者の命は指の間から零れ落ちる
our patients' lives just slip through our fingers.
Death, the ultimate form of science?
死が科学の究極だと？
Bullshit!
巫山戯るな
I'll kill anyone who doesn't value life!
命を大事にしない奴はぶっ殺してやる
I... I remember now.
お…思い出した
You're the Armed Detective Agency's physician,
武装探偵社の専属医　与謝野晶子とはお前か
Yosano Akiko.
My ability, Thou Shalt Not Die,
妾の異能力「君死給勿」は凡る外傷を治癒させる
can cure any wounds.
Even my own wounds, as you can see.
自分の怪我だってほらこの通り
But the necessary conditions are harsh.
ただ条件が厳しくてね
It can only cure lethal injuries.
瀕死の重傷しか治せない
What an inconvenient ability.
不便な力さ
程々の怪我を治そうと思ったら
If I want to cure moderate injuries,
先ずは半殺しにしなきゃならない
I have to half kill my patients first.
おやー
Oh?
You're hurt, aren't you, boy?
怪我してるね　お兄さん
Would you like me to treat you?
治してやろうか
This is
これは…
finished.
終わりだ
My name is Kyouka.
私の名は鏡花
I've killed 35 people.
３５人殺した
Where's the bomb?
爆弾はどこだ
The last victims were a family of three,
一番最後に殺したのは三人家族　父親と母親と男の子
a father, a mother, and a boy.
Demon Snow slit their throats.
夜叉白雪が首を掻き切った
What have you done?!
なんてことを
Who are you?
君はいったい何者なんだ
I can't feel any emotion in your words, nor even in you.
言葉からも君自身からも何の感情も感じない
You're like a murder machine.
まるで殺人機械だ
If you feel anything, you must put it into words.
思いがあるなら言葉にしなきゃ駄目だ
Otherwise, a fool like me won't understand.
じゃないと僕みたいな莫迦にはわからない
Do you really want to go through with this?!
こんなことが本当に君がしたいことなのか
This is the conductor's office.
こちら車掌室
Atsushi!
敦　まだ生きてっかい
You still breathing?
与謝野先生
Dr. Yosano?
According to this frail-ass bomber here,
こっちのヘボ爆弾魔に拠ると　そっちの爆弾は遠隔点火式らしい
your bomb has a remote detonator.
If you make one mistake trying to defuse it,
間違った手段で解除すると数秒で爆発する
it'll explode in a matter of seconds.
You must press the detonator's stop button to defuse it.
解除にはリモコンの停止釦しかない
The Mafia agent there should have it.
そっちのマフィアが持ってる筈だよ
Do you have it?
君が持ってるのか
Give it to me.
渡してくれ
What?!
なんだ
You pressed the button, Kyouka?
それを押したのか　鏡花
Defusing the bomb is unnecessary.
解除など不要　乗客を道連れに
Die along with the passengers
ポートマフィアへの畏怖を俗衆に示せ
and show the pathetic masses that the Port Mafia should be feared.
Take the bomb off!
爆弾を外すんだ
How much time do we have left?!
時間は後どれくらいある
There's no time!
間に合わない
What?
I am a fool, after all.
矢っ張り僕は莫迦だ
I only realized once her slender arms pushed me,
その細い腕に押された時　僕は漸く気づいた
that her ability is always activated by a voice from her cell phone.
彼女の異能力はいつも携帯からの声で動いていた
She's unable to control her own ability.
彼女は自分の異能力を自分で操れないんだ
My name is Kyouka.
私は鏡花　３５人殺した
I've killed 35 people.
I don't want to kill anyone else!
もうこれ以上一人だって殺したくない
Atsushi!
敦
Um...
あの…
No matter how powerful it may be, a pawn is just a pawn.
いくら強くても　駒は駒か
What about you?
貴方はどうだ
Are you a pawn or the master?
駒か　指し手か
Or are you a pawn who is waiting to be crushed?
或いは
砕かれるのを待つ駒か
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
僕が僕でいられる　理由を探していた
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
あなたの胸の中で　生きている僕がいるのならば
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
暗闇も長い坂道も　越えて行けるような僕になれるはず
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
それぞれに今を歩いてる僕らが笑えるように
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
生きている意味を確かめ合いながら進めるように
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
名前を呼ぶよ　あなたの名前を
あなたがあなたでいれるように
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
悲しみに暮れてあなたの涙がこぼれる時
寂しさに溢れて心がしぼんでく時
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
名前を呼ぶよ　あなたの名前を
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
僕の名前を呼んでくれたみたいに
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
She didn't murder by her own free will.
人を殺したのは彼女の意思じゃない
Gifts don't necessarily bring happiness to their wielders.
異能力が当人を倖せにするとは限らない
そんなこと僕が誰よりもわかってる
I know that better than anyone!
でも彼女をこのまま警察に引き渡せば
But if I hand her over to the police,
間違いなく処刑されてしまう
she'll be put to death for sure.
私をどこへ連れてくの
Where are you taking me?
それは…ええと…
That's... um...
Oh, let's go on a date, for starters.
そうだ　取り敢えずデートしよう
Huh?
A date with you?
あなたと？
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 9:
次回　「文豪ストレイドッグス」第九話
The Beauty Is Quiet Like a Stone Statue.
Episode 9
The Beauty is Quiet Like a Stone Statue
「うつくしき人は寂として石像の如く」
Boiled tofu is delicious.
湯豆腐はおいしい